all right scope ease okay so first off
check out our Dooley on technology do
you know only one Eon is on but first
off where are we going we're going a
Home Depot let's type that into our yuan
Hao Depot not home right let's go now
ways
alright scobie's always going to that
let's go do people show up so fast these
things I don't go like on to like
subscribe just this for the Accord no no
this is not funny Cory you're right here
in the comma grab for and we're here to
talk to you about the coma tree the
comet rate not the comma 3 whoa whoa
what's that I don't know no no the comma
tree is a the best way to mount your uh
your your your your GPS your second
grape and on the grape and the base
station yeah so you have to put your
antenna high so we can see the sky and
you don't want it to be interviewed with
by anybody so we are about to build the
common tree we're driving the hardware
store right now I just put Home Depot
into my ways oh oh yeah I made my way
he's not talk cuz I hate when way stalks
don't like being told where to go by
always we have Dooley on technology but
one Jana Jana is broken also broken like
we can turn it on but it's my tactical
Panda and then we need to split her out
again that was just such disaster but
can you show there how nice our focus is
oh yeah our eons now have autofocus
shipping soon
not even soon TM actually soon yeah no
now our eons do not yet stop at red
lights unfortunately let's stop for that
person you're so pretty black seem like
a big outline nice Apple come on they
don't like when you turn them a lot they
get sick get sick you can read out their
questions so there's what we usually do
when he's so he has to buy flowers for
his own hand what does that mean that's
interesting desu yo guys it turns out
that you can use the phase detection
autofocus to determine the length to
things in front of you so all you Subaru
people without radars focus is that
Harold yes that's me and my name is two
days
No well nobody does well the focus is so
good I've never seen the focus be this
good before
this autofocus it is it's actually
really good yeah now it's kind of
focused on the car in front of us
someone says I love you George
thank you does autofocus improve federal
control oh no that's you're gonna have
trouble with new models for that
actually all the focus will improve it a
bit probably yeah um autofocus will
probably help a bit with the ping
ponging issue but no no guys you all
know that this is just the beginning
this is just the beginning we're
starting to get everything super precise
in fact that's what the common tree is
for yeah the comet is amazing yeah by
the way if you guys haven't seen it
right now scope ease go to shop code on
the eye and check out the product shots
of the injection molded panda it looks
so good
Oh somebody asked whether I won in Age
of Empires you practice no I didn't know
I gotta practice a little bit in price
nope it's not anymore
somebody asked when's the new model
where's your lighter and where's your
app Linux okay you want to see where our
applet X's it's right here inside this
gray panda okay this is well we do have
the antenna on the roof though antennas
do work better when we're on the roof
well we have an athletics replacement
it's really almost as good except for
the fact that it doesn't your dual
frequencies how can you see without a
laser point about oh my god okay I don't
know if they're just trolls with the
stupid lighter like honestly bro I mean
I'm not even crazy like Elon agrees with
me and the man ly lands rockets okay
so like I can't be too crazy about this
stuff yeah somebody asked when will
Harold be replaced by AI hopefully not
that soon oh yeah like machine AI is
kind of janky but like that's the thing
you learn about AI if you try to use
like AI for GPS it would be like janky
and whatever break you wouldn't really
know why I would break and like how do
you get good ground truth in the first
place
isn't that true for Harold - I mean yes
yes but it's easier for me to check
Harold's work than to check it oh my god
we don't have the mod yet I've forgot
about hack in the rav4 oh yeah okay we
have reef lashes for the rav4 let me
show you what my reflash can do
unfortunately my speed is too low right
now but you see that set speed it says
zero miles an hour we can turn our
cruise control on at zero miles an hour
unfortunately it still doesn't
accelerate will show the Scopus you can
put the cruise control all the way down
all right wait doesn't accelerate from a
full stop well no you but the cruise
control all the way down to zero but it
doesn't do anything because the only
thing we've actually managed to change
was like the number that it says all
right so we made the wrong patch so this
rav4 is actually running custom firmware
but it's running wrong custom firmware
so does that freak you out does this
work for a home data core 2018 that's a
bad question
go get it does it work I don't know bro
what are you gonna make it work you all
do agile process animates Oh a job I
read a book about that it's like like
scrum you know some people do scrum as
well wait I don't even know the right
way
oh we got a good of John Daly oh my god
is this by the loop good yeah it's like
a few miles south somebody asks I'll p2k
if you put it on out EA six to the
bounty good bounty for how to get forced
out EA sixes use flexpay as well so all
like the high-end German caught is that
like people actually want to drive use
flex pay flex right kind of sucks wait
why there two antennas here well this
was the antenna testing oh so many does
the retail store have a parking lot do
we have a retail store retail store yeah
you were there for the night at the
retail store yeah is that a thing yeah
it's happening really did you call them
oh this is amazing everyone if they give
they give you a good deal like honestly
I was on the staff and like they're like
wow you want a retail store what
business objectives does it achieve and
then I told them that I hated business
again it's fun yes exactly
somebody asked that you can hang out in
module cars in the parking lot yeah of
course yeah you're welcome
like let's just take over West portable
yeah exactly somebody asks for stickers
for their car well if you buy call my
products in it stickers that's true
and I'm willing to contribute to the
Audi bounty great yeah I mean I don't
think it's gonna matter really how much
of a bounty be put on Audi's because
flex pays too hard there's a bounty up
for a flex return Seaver - like that's
the first step someone needs to build a
flex panda Oh relax and wait the Panda
doesn't receive flex right okay where's
the comma tree well the comma tree is in
Home Depot right now yeah we're gonna go
buy it
we're buying a 4x4 like a big thick wood
you know it's like a two-by-four but but
what if we just bought two two by fours
and nailed them together that's still
wobbly I think no they'd be nailed
together even why would we did buy a 4x4
that's a good point
how about you get it home it sounds like
a shitty fool I mean what's the
difference being
like it's just thicker right our size
limitation is by two four by fours and
then bolt them together we'll get some
like steel things kind of we could do
that yeah call my tree projects they're
taking them a lot of time to come a tree
project through Oregon
you don't be nice if on the open pilot
screen it showed you your directions
that'd be nice if anyone out there from
commenting eyes watching I complain
about bugs some time on the periscope -
I hope somebody's watching most people
watch it somebody says just buy a fence
post well that's exactly what we're
doing buying a big thick fence post yes
um so we were originally gonna put the
antenna on the roof but the roof at the
calm imagined it being a mansion normal
is very steep um so we call some people
and we send some pictures and they were
afraid to go on the roof I was about to
go on the roof myself
do you guys know I'm a maverick I would
do it oh wait you send pictures in there
like that no they sent pictures and they
were like now yeah that's Yeah right I
thought that's what these people's jobs
so what I saw - and like I don't know
man I think I could make a living if I
just like you haven't watched like dying
Mama's YouTube videos and there's real
calling is coming on roofs and filming
shit right somebody's asked me what I
think although that might by the way
shout out dying llama we haven't have to
go to level support in our code because
um you know you know you know they're
asking you know what we do during a
climb that's right but I hope so yeah we
disengage we don't believe it's
appropriate for computers to make
ethical determinations it's two two by
fours smaller than a four by four No -
two by fours is exactly this big is it
for life is that true because no two
avoids on a 2x4 right wait they're not
if you don't know the scam no they're
1.75 big 3.5 but that's a big difference
so you don't know about the too much
horse camp I don't know if this is true
about four by fours like I kind of feel
four by fours are actually four by four
because I kind of feel like that wider
than a two by four that's it somebody
says a four by four is three point five
times three points okay fine it really
is just two two by fours bolted together
that's how they make for my force
turns you need Python programmers of
just JavaScript ah if you are just
honestly all we really care about is if
you're intelligent motivated if you are
intelligent motivated and like though
honestly if you're like intelligent
motivated I don't care if you don't know
it doesn't matter just just like for
example the autofocus stuff I've been
doing it right it doesn't require any
special skill you just need to like
don't be smart and persistent and stuff
um so if you can do that well I give me
a job of calming I will check like your
getup stars and stuff got a lot of stars
I get out pretty good I mean like look
guys you here's like the things that we
here's like the skills that we we value
okay so we look at where you went to
college and then we probably forget
about that because nobody cares um and
then we ask you questions like how long
does it take light to travel a foot did
you go right yeah okay I mean these are
like good things to know right it's
useful knowledge somebody says this
angles not very flattering for George
well I'm sorry I'm not a very good
cameraman I mean it's just kind of your
face is half black kind of look like a
half of the car bro this car is actually
running custom firmware right now yeah I
know right
no but the new model is gonna be so much
better to look in focus on us
yeah it's never been in focus before
this is better than the slider you guys
and all these improvements are of course
coming completely free to your yawns I
can auto focus is $3 deal say um no
seriously oh but it's about to get I
mean not for a bit you're gonna have to
wait a bit but by the end of the year if
you get the hardware now you get it
installed in your car by the end of the
year what open palette 0.5 comes out
you're gonna be like wow that was what
of what an incredible shift life
distance is measured in meters not feet
and it depends on what are we doing
today well we're going to build a common
tree country which is a base station for
your gray panda yeah you got to put your
great pan to antenna where it has a good
view of the sky and it's unobstructed by
trees so this is generally high up and
if you want to get things high up you
need a big pole and we're gonna buy a
big pole I mean we could provide a real
tree but real trees wobble fake trees
are better 3.5 times 3.5 it's been ADEA
somebody says the internet says one
nanosecond will yeah that sounds about
right that's two now like okay you know
it's like no understand intuitive
physics right what's the difference
between a camera on a ladder
cameras use light music's lidar has a
laser is that what makes light our work
how does light our work I don't know if
you answer that question too precisely
you'll get to by whele will you release
the custom firmware oh for the rav4 yes
as soon as it works bro yeah we will
release Oh Panda Express we tweeted at
them on Twitter to try to get them to be
the exclusive IRL distributor of the
kava ai Panda they didn't tweet back at
us unfortunately but if anyone you want
to go inside and ask we have like some
retail packages and what we'll do that
on periscope no well do that on YouTube
we'll do that for the kama vlog yeah
[Laughter]
this is funnier than coning planking of
wagang was great with that side yeah
that's what the school wasn't too happy
about my planking
that's what PewDiePie said a meme isn't
a 10 out of 10 until somebody died
[Laughter]
alright guys thank you for joining us on
the drive to the Home Depot sure to uh
like you know hit that subscribe button
below subscribe a periscope right
midnight blackity on shipping the
fifteenth absolutely bro everything is
shipping the 15th Eddie has been working
super hard Eddie if you're out there
watching back to work oh yeah it's been
doing a great job
everything's gonna show up even great
pandas by the 15th so get your orders in
today shop comma dot ai you know where
to go more scope e scopes yes I love the
scope ease man you guys are the
strongest family on periscope you guys
too
now see I don't get angry you gotta
really like these aren't flattering
angles fighting I love you guys too I
love the scope ease bye bye see ya